Ericks Espinoza Gómez

ericksespinoza1@gmail.com

Phone +57 320 8294033

Bogotá DC - Colombia.

https://github.com/eespinoza1

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ericks-espinoza-g%C3%B3mez-58b9b8231/

I am Full Stack Web Developer, i was senior auditor in a bank, managing databases and generating reports. i am a passionate about software development, always oriented to the good use of information. My Profile is PERN oriented the Backend.

I also have experience as a community manager in the control of advertising campaign statistics with Facebook ads and Google ads from various companies.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Web Developer- Teaching Assistant 11/2022 – 02/2023

Henry Bootcamp, Buenos Aires, Argentina.

- Coordinate a group student to achieve integration to study group.
- Guide Students in the first steps of the course.
- Assist to solve exercisers and promote group collaboration (Pair Programming).
- Propose ideas to improve the Bootcamp processes.

Community Manager-Accountant

02/2017-12/2022

Riot Custom Apparel

- Database administration.
- Advertising through Facebook ads and Google ads and design of advertising campaigns.
- Elaboration of accounting accounts in excel and access.

Senior financial auditor

05/2011-06/2016

Banesco Universal Bank, Maracay, Venezuela.

- develop an inventory and returned check control system encourage the use of electronic channels.
- To make database reports on the financial behavior of users.
- Minimize the organization's equity risk to ensure business continuity.

PROFESSIONAL EDUCATION

- Full Stack Developer. Henry Bootcamp. 2022-2023.
- Accountant. Universidad Nacional Experimental de las Fuerzas Armadas. 2005 2010.
- Certification of Javascript algorithms and data structures. FreeCodeCamp (In progress 2023).

PROJECTS

Ecommerce - www.alanastore.store

04/2023

Freelancer, Maracay, Venezuela.

- Design a scalable database in strapi.
- Develop a department store containing categories and sub-categories of the products in react
- I made a shopping cart with redux
- Apply a user friendly and easy to use scss layout.

Streaming Music - "https://henrymusic.tech/"

02/2023

Henry Bootcamp, Buenos Aires, Argentina.

- We use two Apis (google and Spotify), one to get the music and the other to get the data of the albums, artist, year, name of the song.
- The database was made in postgres and the backend with express, multer, axios, sequelize and JWT. The relationships allow to create a playlist per user and other middlewares.
- In the Front-end we use html, react, redux and bootstrap.

Technologies

Expert

HTML, Css (Bootstrap, Material UI), Javascript, React, Redux, Redux Toolkit, Node Js / Express, AS400, Sequelize, Postgres, Strapi and MySql.

Basic

Python, MongoDb, GitHub, Docker, servers Nginx, payment platform integrations an Json web token.

Languages

- English B2 Intermediate.
- Spanish Native